trinetexpense.com 2018-08-31

# TriNet Expense - Pages

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy applies to the websites www.ExpenseCloud.com, www.TriNetPerform.com, www.TriNetExpense.com, www.TriNetTravel.com, www.TriNetMarketPlace.com, and www.TriNetHire.com, owned and operated by TriNet Group Inc. and its subsidiaries (“TriNet,” “TriNet Cloud”). This privacy policy describes how TriNet collects and uses the personal information you provide on our websites. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. 

Protecting the privacy of users of TriNet Cloud products is important to TriNet. TriNet makes use of any personal information you provide to TriNet only for the purposes outlined in this policy. To the extent TriNet's International Privacy Policy ("International Policy") is also applicable to your personal information and if there is any conflict between the terms of this policy and the International Policy, the terms of the International Policy will govern. 

This policy does not apply to any information that you may provide directly to third parties including via third-party sites linked to the TriNet Cloud websites. While TriNet actively seeks to ensure that its suppliers and service providers maintain high standards regarding the protection of personal information collected on their websites, TriNet is not responsible for the privacy practices employed by such third-party sites. 

## Information We Collect

The TriNet Cloud websites collect contact, billing, financial, demographic and other identifying information. We, TriNet, will never sell, rent, lend or trade this information in our possession to any other company for the purpose of contacting you regarding commercial services. If you are a TriNet Cloud user, we collect the information necessary to provide our services, collecting it either from you directly or from your employer. This collection is limited to the purpose of providing the service for which you or your employer have engaged TriNet. By voluntarily providing information or by accessing our websites, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and, if applicable, the International Policy. When you download and/or use our services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or "UDID"). 

## Usage Tracking and Cookies

We track user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites, but this tracking is never associated with non-registered individual users. We compile aggregate data mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you go to next (whether this URL is on our site or not), and what browser and computing platform you are using. 

In addition, we use cookies on certain pages of our sites. We may also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. Cookies enable you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide you information that is targeted to your interests. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our sites. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. We also use persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time and remembers your preferences. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our sites, and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session.The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, and service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our sites. 

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on our sites, we may collect and store such information in a file specific to you. If you submit questions via our sites, we may post your questions on the sites, and reprint them in various articles and customer communications. We will never include the name, contact or other identifiable information of people who submit questions, regardless of which channel we use to distribute content. 

## Use of Information

We use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze site usage, improve our content product offerings, customize our sites' content, layout and services, and provide our services. 

We may use the email address, mailing address, and phone number we collect from you to respond to your inquiries and, to the extent permitted by applicable law, to contact you regarding administrative notices, new product offerings and communications relevant to your use of our sites. In some cases, we may use your personally identifiable information to inform you of new services, promotions and other matters targeted to your interests. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preference settings of anyaccount you have with us or by contacting us at TriNetCloud@TriNet.com. We use information in the file we maintain specific to you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on our sites, to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes and we may evaluate information about you to look for users using multiple User IDs or aliases. 

## Disclosure of Information

Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, respond to a government request, or respond to any other third party request with your prior consent to do so. 

Third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Therefore, although we employ industry-standard practices to protect your privacy, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. 

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services. As a general proposition, we do not sell, rent, lend or trade any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. The following paragraphs describe some of the ways that personally identifiable information about you may be disclosed to third parties. 

## Legal Requests

We cooperate with law enforcement and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property rights and other rights. Therefore, local, state, federal, territorial, provincial and international law enforcement can request and may receive your personally identifiable information. By your use of TriNet Cloud websites or TriNet's services (as applicable), you hereby accept these terms and you authorize us to disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. 

## Business Transactions

We reserve the right to transfer personally identifiable information as part of a sale or transfer of all or a relevant portion of our business or assets. Any such sale would be subject to appropriate privacy protections for you. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information. Suppliers and Other Service Providers 

We may use third-party suppliers and service providers to facilitate provision of our TriNet Cloud Services. For example, we may outsource the operations of one or more aspects of our sites to a supplier or service provider who performs services according to our requirements. In all cases, we restrict how these suppliers and other service providers may access, use and disclose information received from our sites. We do not permit these suppliers and other service providers to access information about you, other than that information necessary for them to complete the services for which they are contracted. Under no circumstances do we allow them to disclose, sell, rent, lend, trade or in any other way transmit data about you to third parties, and we use contractual means to require them to provide appropriate protection for your personally identifiable information and to use it only for the services for which they are contracted. 

## Retention of Information

We retain personally identifiable information that we collect only so long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected and to meet legal requirements. In certain cases, information is required to be retained indefinitely. We have a Business Record Retention Policy and an E- mail Retention Policy which provide for the destruction of personally identifiable information after it is no longer needed for the purposes for which it was collected and legal requirements have been met. 

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at TriNetCloud@TriNet.com. 

## Referrals

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. You must have the consent of your friend to provide us with this information. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. This email will identify that you asked for it to be sent. TriNet may store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at TriNetCloud@trinet.com to request that we remove this information from our database. 

## Social Media Widgets

Our website includes social media features, such as the Facebook button, and widgets, such as the ShareThis button, or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## Changes in this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time without prior notice to users of this site. This Privacy Policy was last updated on Feb 3, 2014. Please check here regularly to learn of any changes to this policy. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

## Copyright Notification

ExpenseCloud, TriNet Marketplace, TriNet Perform, TriNet Hire, TriNet Travel and TriNet Expense are the property of TriNet. • ©2014, All rights reserved. 

## Trademark Information

The TriNet logo and design are registered trademarks of TriNet. All other trademarks, trade names, service marks and logos appearing on this website belong to their respective companies. 

## Contact Information

TriNet

1100 San Leandro Boulevard

Suite 400

San Leandro, CA 94577, USA

legal@TriNet.com
